ibpsexamadda.org.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You may wish to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site and/or your registration for any of our products or services constitutes an acceptance of this privacy policy.

http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in uses cookies to personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a server and stored in your web browser. Cookies cannot be used to deliver viruses to your computer and do not run programs. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a domain of the web server that issued the cookie to you.

Third-party vendors, including Google uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting advertising opt-out page here: [Google’s ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).Third-party vendors, including Google, also use cookies to serve ads on our website based on a user’s prior visits.

Additionally, users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter or RSS by providing their name and email address to get access to articles, videos and/or ebooks. We use a secure double opt-in subscription method, and we reserve the right to contact those subscribers with information related to our website. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime, and every email delivered will contain a link which can be used for that purpose.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in and its parent network.

http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in is not responsible for the content of external internet sites it connects to. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

**This website uses the Google AdWords Remarketing Service**  
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the http://www.IBPSExamAdda.org.in website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).

Please contact those internet sites/vendors and others directly if you have any queries about their privacy policies.

For any other information or concerns, please connect to us through the following page: [Connect to IBPS Exam Adda team for privacy policy related queries](http://www.ibpsexamadda.org.in/contact).

– IBPS Exam Adda Editorial Team
